(this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]=this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]||[]).push([[0],{25:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},45:function(e,t,n){},46:function(e,t,n){},51:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var r=n(2),a=n(0),s=n.n(a),i=n(11),o=n.n(i),c=(n(45),n.p,n(46),n(12)),l=n(13),h=n(16),u=n(14),d=n(25),p=n(71),m=n(72),j=n(73),b=n(74),x=n(69);function y(e){return Object(r.jsx)(x.a,{style:{minHeight:"80px"},variant:"h6",gutterBottom:!0,children:e.text.toString().replace(/%20/g," ").replace(/%3F/g,"?").replace(/%2C/g,",").replace(/%22/g,'"').replace(/%27/g,"'")})}function f(e){return Object(r.jsx)(x.a,{variant:"h6",color:"textSecondary",gutterBottom:!0,children:e.text.toString().replace(/%20/g," ").replace(/%3A/,":").replace(/%26/,"&")})}var g=n(75);function w(e){var t=0;return"hard"==e.text?t=3:"easy"==e.text?t=1:"medium"==e.text&&(t=2),Object(r.jsx)(g.a,{size:"small",name:"read-only",value:t,readOnly:!0})}var O=n(26),v=function(e){Object(h.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(e){var r;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(r=t.call(this,e)).check=function(e){r.props.check(e),r.props.Invoke_Revoke(!0)},r}return Object(l.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return Object(r.jsxs)(p.a,{container:!0,spacing:1,alignContent:"centre",children:[Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:1}),this.props.text.map((function(t,n){var a;return Object(r.jsx)(p.a,(a={item:!0,sm:!0},Object(O.a)(a,"item",!0),Object(O.a)(a,"xs",10),Object(O.a)(a,"children",Object(r.jsx)(b.a,{size:"small",style:{minWidth:"200px"},variant:"contained",color:"primary",disabled:e.props.IsInvokAns,onClick:function(){return e.check(t)},children:t.toString().replace(/%20/g," ").replace(/%24/g,"$").replace(/%2C/g,",")})),a),n)})),Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:1})]})}}]),n}(a.Component),_=function(e){Object(h.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(e){var r;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(r=t.call(this,e)).checkans=function(e){e==r.props.data.correct_answer?(r.setState({SuccessLabel:"Correct..!"}),r.props.score(!0)):(r.setState({SuccessLabel:"Incorrect."}),r.props.score(!1)),r.props.AllowNext(!1)},r.StopAns=function(e){return r.setState({Stop:e})},r.shuffle=function(e){for(var t,n,r=e.length;0!==r;)n=Math.floor(Math.random()*r),t=e[r-=1],e[r]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e},r.componentDidUpdate=function(e){return e.data!=r.props.data?r.setState({SuccessLabel:"",opt:r.shuffle(r.props.data.incorrect_answers.concat(r.props.data.correct_answer))}):null},r.state={Stop:!1,SuccessLabel:"",opt:r.shuffle(r.props.data.incorrect_answers.concat(r.props.data.correct_answer))},r}return Object(l.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(r.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(r.jsx)(f,{text:this.props.data.category}),Object(r.jsx)(w,{text:this.props.data.difficulty}),Object(r.jsx)(y,{text:this.props.data.question}),Object(r.jsx)("hr",{}),Object(r.jsx)(v,{text:this.state.opt,check:this.checkans,StopAns:this.StopAns,IsInvokAns:this.props.IsInvokAns,Invoke_Revoke:this.props.Invoke_Revoke}),Object(r.jsx)("h1",{children:this.state.SuccessLabel})]})}}]),n}(a.Component),S=n(76),k=function(e){Object(h.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(e){var r;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(r=t.call(this,e)).setNext=function(){return r.setState({Stepper:r.state.Stepper+1,DisableNext:!0,IsInvokAns:!1})},r.AllowNext=function(e){return r.setState({DisableNext:e})},r.getScore=function(e){return e?r.setState({countRight:r.state.countRight+1}):r.setState({countWrong:r.state.countWrong+1})},r.Invoke_Revoke=function(e){return r.setState({IsInvokAns:e})},r.showbtn=function(e){return r.setState({btndis:e})},r.state={questions:d.map((function(e){return e.question})),C_Answer:d.map((function(e){return e.correct_answer})),AllowNext:!1,IsInvokAns:!1,Stepper:0,countRight:0,countWrong:0,DisableNext:!0},r}return Object(l.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.state,t=e.countRight,n=e.countWrong,a=e.IsInvokAns,s=e.Stepper,i=e.questions,o=t/i.length*100,c=t/s*100;return Number.isNaN(c)&&(c=0),Number.isFinite(c)||(c=0),Object(r.jsx)("div",{style:{margin:"20px"},children:s<i.length?Object(r.jsxs)(p.a,{container:!0,spacing:3,children:[Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:2}),Object(r.jsxs)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:8,children:[Object(r.jsx)(m.a,{variant:"determinate",value:5*s,style:{height:"15px"}}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsxs)(x.a,{variant:"h5",children:["Question ",s+1," of ",i.length]}),Object(r.jsx)(j.a,{style:{minHeight:"270px"},elevation:1,children:Object(r.jsx)(_,{data:d[s],AllowNext:this.AllowNext,Invoke_Revoke:this.Invoke_Revoke,IsInvokAns:a,score:this.getScore})}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)(b.a,{style:{float:"right"},size:"large",color:"secondary",variant:"contained",onClick:this.setNext,disabled:this.state.DisableNext,children:"NEXT"}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsxs)("h5",{children:["Score ",parseInt(c),"%"]}),Object(r.jsxs)(S.a,{children:[Object(r.jsx)(S.a,{striped:!0,variant:"success",now:o},1),Object(r.jsx)(S.a,{variant:"warning",now:c},2)]}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)(S.a,{striped:!0,variant:"success",now:100,style:{height:"5px",width:"100px"}})," Percent",Object(r.jsx)(S.a,{striped:!0,variant:"warning",now:100,style:{height:"5px",width:"100px"}})," Score"]}),Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:2}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{})]}):Object(r.jsxs)(p.a,{container:!0,spacing:3,children:[Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:2}),Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:8,children:Object(r.jsx)(j.a,{style:{minHeight:"350px",marginTop:"20px"},elevation:5,children:Object(r.jsxs)(p.a,{container:!0,spacing:3,children:[Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:2}),Object(r.jsxs)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:8,children:[Object(r.jsxs)("h4",{children:["  ",Object(r.jsx)("b",{children:" Thankyou for taking this Quiz."})]}),Object(r.jsx)("hr",{}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{}),Object(r.jsx)(x.a,{variant:"h6",children:"Exam Details : "}),Object(r.jsx)("hr",{}),Object(r.jsxs)("h6",{children:["Total Question: ",Object(r.jsx)("b",{style:{margin:"100px"},children:i.length})]}),Object(r.jsxs)("h6",{children:["Total Correct Answer(s):",Object(r.jsx)("b",{style:{margin:"40px"},children:t})]}),Object(r.jsxs)("h6",{children:["Total Wrong Answer(s):",Object(r.jsx)("b",{style:{margin:"40px"},children:n})]}),Object(r.jsxs)("h6",{children:["Percentage:",Object(r.jsxs)("b",{style:{margin:"40px"},children:[o," %"]})]}),Object(r.jsxs)("h6",{children:["Over All Score:",Object(r.jsxs)("b",{style:{margin:"40px"},children:[c," "]})]}),Object(r.jsxs)("h6",{children:["Grade:",Object(r.jsxs)("b",{style:{margin:"40px"},children:[o>50?"Normal (above 50 or higher)":"Failed (less then 50 or lowest)"," "]})]}),Object(r.jsx)("hr",{}),Object(r.jsx)("h6",{children:"This App is Developed By : Muhammad Abu Baker"})]}),Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:2})]})})}),Object(r.jsx)(p.a,{item:!0,xs:2}),Object(r.jsx)("br",{})]})})}}]),n}(a.Component);var A=function(){return Object(r.jsx)("div",{children:Object(r.jsx)(k,{})})},C=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,77)).then((function(t){var n=t.getCLS,r=t.getFID,a=t.getFCP,s=t.getLCP,i=t.getTTFB;n(e),r(e),a(e),s(e),i(e)}))};o.a.render(Object(r.jsx)(s.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(r.jsx)(A,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),C()}},[[51,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.07ab1b75.chunk.js.map